[{"question": " hey, you guys! ross and rachel: hey!", "answer": " so, what do you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " about what?", "answer": " yeah, what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " are you kidding? okay, i&#146;ll give you a hint; i&#146;ll give you a hint.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " eyes! no, no. your eyes! no. chandler&#146;s eyes!", "answer": " i got glasses!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " well, you-you&#146;ve always had glasses.", "answer": " no i didn&#146;t!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " yeah-yeah, did-didn&#146;t you use to have a pair? they were really round, burgundy, and they made you look kind of umm&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " feminine.", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " sweetie, i think the glasses look great. they make you look really sexy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  you didn&#146;t think i used to wear glasses, right?", "answer": " of course!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " so what do you guys want for an engagement present?", "answer": " that&#146;s okay pheebs, we&#146;re not having a party or anything, so you don&#146;t have to get us&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  if someone wants to give us a present, we don&#146;t want to deprive them of that joy.", "answer": " oh, y&#146;know what you should get &#145;em? one of those little uh, portable cd players.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh, i already have one.", "answer": " not unless someone borrowed it and left it at the gynecologist.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " yeah, and-and-and by someone, she means joey.", "answer": " hey, i know i what i want!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " what we want honey.", "answer": " no, you don&#146;t want this. i want to have your grandmother&#146;s cookie recipe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " you mean the chocolate chip cookie recipe?", "answer": " uh-huh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " you mean the one that my grandmother made me swear on her deathbed that i would never let out of our family?", "answer": " dying people say the craziest things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " i wanted it for years! i was gonna make cookies for my children.", "answer": " break my heart&#151;oh, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " okay. i&#146;m gonna be the mom that makes the world&#146;s best chocolate chip cookies.", "answer": " our kids are gonna be fat aren&#146;t they.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  ahoy!", "answer": " hey! how&#146;s the boat?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " great! i&#146;m finally getting into this sailing stuff.", "answer": " oh, so you finally took it out of the marina huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " why would i do that? it took three guys to get the thing in there!", "answer": " if you don&#146;t sail your boat, what do you do on it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well, it&#146;s good that you finally have a place to do that.", "answer": " y&#146;know joey, i could teach you to sail if you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " you could?", "answer": " yeah! i&#146;ve been sailing my whole life. when i was fifteen my dad bought me my own boat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " your own boat?", "answer": " what?! what?! he was trying to cheer me up! my pony was sick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " do you know what i was thinkin&#146;?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  hey chandler, what are you doing tonight?", "answer": " uh why, do you have a lecture?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " no, why?", "answer": " then free as a bird. what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " my dad wanted to know if you wanted to play racquetball with us.", "answer": " wow! that&#146;s great! dad must really like you, he doesn&#146;t ask just anyone to play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " yeah and he didn&#146;t really ask for you, he asked for chancy, i assumed he meant you.", "answer": " well, did-did you correct him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " no, i-i thought it would be more fun this way.", "answer": " this is so cool, maybe this is something you can do every week.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " or you can sit with him on the front porch and make sure no one steals the trash cans. he does that every week too.", "answer": " oh, just so you know, you-you have to let him win.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " he hates to lose.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh no problem, maybe i&#146;ll play with my left hand.", "answer": " you&#146;re not a lefty?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what&#146;s wrong phoebe?", "answer": " i just went to my old apartment to get you the-the cookie recipe and the stupid fire burned it up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " no!! why didn&#146;t you make a copy and-and keep it in a fireproof box and keep it at least a hundred yards from the original?!!", "answer": "  because i&#146;m normal! that was the one legacy my grandmother left me, and i know you wanted it as an engagement present.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, we have to get you an engagement present?", "answer": " don&#146;t worry about it pheebs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " no one got me an engagement present.", "answer": " okay, here i wish you health and happiness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " an old cookie?", "answer": "  this is what happens when you don&#146;t register for gifts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " see no-no, i made a batch and i froze it, and this is the only one left.", "answer": " we can&#146;t accept this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " &#145;cause it&#146;s gross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " no! wait! i think i can figure out the recipe from this cookie! i do stuff like this at work all the time.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay, we owe you a present.", "answer": " two! i&#146;ve been engaged twice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  look at this clown! just because he&#146;s got a bigger boat he thinks he can take up the whole river.  get out of the way jackass!  who names his boat coast guard anyway?", "answer": " that is the coast guard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " joey, just ignore the boats all right? we&#146;re not finished with the lesson yet.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay, i&#146;m just gonna go over the basic points just one more time, are you ready?", "answer": " come on rach, not again. i got it! okay? let&#146;s start sailing, and i want to go over there  where that boatload of girls is!  yo-ho-ho!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh, okay. is that what you want to do? you wanna go over and give a little shout out to the old, hot chickas? okay, let&#146;s do that sailor joe. quick question though,  what&#146;s this called?", "answer": " uh, boat rope.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " wrong! how do you get the mainsail up?", "answer": " uhh, rub it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no. what do you do if i say we are coming about?", "answer": " i&#146;d say, come again. no-no, wait i-i-i know this one, i know this one, uh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " time&#146;s up, now your dead.", "answer": " and deaf!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " don&#146;t just say yes! this isn&#146;t a game, joey you can really get hurt out here. okay, so do you want to pay attention or do you want to die?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " all right, i definitely taste nutmeg.", "answer": " you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " you don&#146;t?  well, that&#146;s the difference between a professional and a layman.", "answer": " that and arrogance.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey! how was sailing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i don&#146;t want to talk about it. y&#146;know, you could&#146;ve at least saved me a whole cookie.  monica and phoebe: no-wait-no-no!!!!!!!", "answer": "  women are mean!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe that! now the only thing left of my grandmother&#146;s legacy is this crumb.  i wish you a long and happy marriage.", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey! how was it?", "answer": " well i had a great time! umm, chancy on the other hand&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " i will tell the story! it was going great. i let him win. we were bonding. he even said i could call him dad.", "answer": " and what did he ask you not to call him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " guys?", "answer": " over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh my god chandler! i can&#146;t believe it!", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " you gave my father a lap dance!", "answer": " why do they put so much steam in there?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " &#145;cause otherwise they&#146;d have to call it the room room.", "answer": " why? okay? why? wh-wh-why did that have to happen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " come on, it&#146;s not that big a deal!", "answer": " not that big a deal? there&#133;there was touching of things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " now, i know you wanted to bond with my dad, but did you really have to bond to that part?", "answer": " listen, i&#146;m sure that dad doesn&#146;t care. he probably thought this was funny; he&#146;ll be telling this story for years!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i don&#146;t want him to tell this story for years.", "answer": " oh, but he will. he still tells the story how monica tried to escape from fat camp.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " i wasn&#146;t escaping.", "answer": " then how did you get caught in the barbed wire?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " i was trying to help out a squirrel.", "answer": " you were trying to eat it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " if that is your father calling to tell this story then the marriage is off!", "answer": "  come on.  hello?  i&#146;m sorry you have the wrong number.   okay, i&#146;ll call you later dad. i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  all right, i&#146;m off to see your dad.", "answer": " whoa-whoa, aren&#146;t you a little over dressed?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  yeah, and-and you better make sure he tips you this time.", "answer": " look, i figured i would try to convince him not to tell the story anymore, and i figure the best way to do that is face to face&#151;and by face i don&#146;t mean his lap. and by face, i don&#146;t mean my ass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  hey are you getting monica and chandler an engagement present?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. y&#146;know, they didn&#146;t get us anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " thank you!", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " well hello! so, when are we gettin&#146; back out on the water matey?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " oh uh, i don&#146;t know the boat way to say this, but uh never!", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " because! you&#146;re mean on the boat!", "answer": " what? i was just trying to teach you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " well, lesson learned! rachel is mean!", "answer": " yeeeeeep&#133; yep-yep-yep-yep-yep. i remember when she took out on her dad&#146;s boat she wouldn&#146;t let me help at all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " excuse me, i wanted you to help, but you couldn&#146;t move your arms because you were wearing three life jackets.", "answer": " you have to respect the sea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " look joey, i&#146;m sorry if-if you thought that was mean, but i gotta tell ya something. that was not mean. okay, my father is mean. he used to yell at me all the time on the boat, i mean it was horrible. i was just being a good teacher.", "answer": " does a good teacher say, &quot;put down the beer pinhead!?&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well, does a good student drink seven beers during his first lesson?", "answer": " six and a half! you knocked that last one out of my hand! remember?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " yeah, i didn&#146;t want you to get hit by the boom!", "answer": " well it hit me anyway! and it would&#146;ve hurt a lot less if i had finished that last beer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " all right, y&#146;know what? i-i&#146;m sorry. i will try to tone it down and uh stop yelling.", "answer": " you won&#146;t boss me around anymore?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " i won&#146;t boss you around.", "answer": " and you&#146;ll be nice?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " and, i&#146;ll be nice.", "answer": " and you&#146;ll be topless?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " and&#151;joey!", "answer": " do you want me to learn?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " okay, here&#146;s batch 22. ohh, maybe these&#146;ll taste a little like your grandmother&#146;s. this has a little bit of orange peel, but no nutmeg.", "answer": " let&#146;s give it a shot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " okay. man, i have not made this many cookies since i was in the ninth grade.", "answer": " oh, what was that for? like a bake sale?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " ohh, these are pretty good.", "answer": " yeah, but not as good as batch 17.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " which one was that?", "answer": " the ones we had right after you almost threw up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh yeah! batch 17 was good. i did not like batch 16.  i&#146;m okay.", "answer": " are there anymore from the good batch? &#145;cause we could just work off of those.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " okay joey honey, you&#146;re doing really good! all right, now i&#146;m just gonna need you to step to the port side.  remember? remember how we talked about the port side?", "answer": " ohh yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " right?", "answer": " nope.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " it&#146;s left sweetie, but that&#146;s okay sweetie, that&#146;s a tough one.", "answer": " i don&#146;t know why you just don&#146;t say left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " okay, go to the left.  the left!", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  okay! okay, you&#146;re yelling again! see that?", "answer": " no! no-no, no-no-no, very quiet, said with love, no yelling.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " uh, wow, you just said a bunch of stuff i didn&#146;t know there.", "answer": " joey, come on! we just went over this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh, y&#146;know, when we did that was when that bird was flying overhead with the fish in his mouth. did you see it? it was gross!", "answer": "  no! all right?! i did not see the bird! i did not see the fish! i did not see the piece of styrofoam that was shaped like mike tyson! i did not, because i was trying to teach you how to sail a boat! which obviously is an impossible thing to do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " all right that&#146;s it! you&#146;re yelling and i don&#146;t see you taking your top off! i quit!", "answer": " what do you mean you quit?! you can&#146;t quit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " why not?!", "answer": " because you&#146;re not finished yet and i won&#146;t have it! greens do not quit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " greens? i&#146;m a tribbiani! and tribbianis quit!", "answer": " oh my god, wait did i&#151;i just said greens don&#146;t quit didn&#146;t i?   did i just say greens don&#146;t quit?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " yes! yes! you did and you&#146;re still yelling at me!", "answer": " no! no! no! i&#146;m not yelling at you, i&#146;m just yelling near you. oh god joey, ohh i&#146;m my father. oh my god, this is horrible! i&#146;ve been trying so hard not to be my mother i did not see this comin&#146;. oh, joey, i&#146;m sorry. i&#146;m so sorry. i just wanted you to learn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " well, hey i did learn.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " yeah! come on.", "answer": " awww&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah, it&#146;s okay. i know what a mainsail is.  i know, i know to duck when the boom comes across. i-i know port is right.", "answer": " left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i bet it would actually make my grandmother very happy to know that we&#146;re trying to figure out her recipe. i bet she&#146;s l-l-lookin&#146; up at us and smiling right now.", "answer": " looking up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh yeah&#151;no, she was really nice to me, but she&#146;s in hell for sure.", "answer": " well, i&#146;ve tried everything. i give up. i guess i&#146;m not gonna be the mom who makes the world&#146;s best chocolate cookies. i do make the best duck confit with broccoli rabe. kids love that right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " aww, pheeb, come on isn&#146;t there any relative that would have the recipe? what about, what about your sister?", "answer": " oh no-no, no, i made a promise to myself that the next time i would talk to ursula would be over my dead body. and that&#146;s not happening &#145;til october 15th, 2032.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " that&#146;s the day you&#146;re gonna die? see&#151;darnit, i&#146;ve got shuffleboard that day.", "answer": " that&#146;s what you think.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " well, i mean what about friends of your grandmother&#146;s? wouldn&#146;t they have the recipe?", "answer": " well, y&#146;know i may have relatives in france who would know. my grandmother said she got the recipe from her grandmother, nesele tolouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " what was her name?", "answer": " nesele toulouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " nestle tollhouse?!", "answer": " oh, you americans always butcher the french language.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": "  yes!!  ohh.", "answer": " i cannot believe that i just spent the last two days trying to figure out the recipe and it was in my cupboard the whole time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " so you understand, i&#146;d feel a lot more comfortable if you didn&#146;t tell people what happened. y&#146;know, i&#146;m a little&#133;i&#146;m a little embarrassed about it.", "answer": " i understand completely, there&#146;s nothing more horrifying than embarrassing yourself in front of your in-laws. as a matter of fact, when i started dating judy i was unemployed, and her father asked me what i did for a living and i told him i was a lawyer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " what did you do when they found out?", "answer": " they never did, so if ever see me giving them legal advice just nod along. shall we?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " well joey, i hate to admit it, your way of sailing is a lot more fun.", "answer": " yeah, yeah. hey, why don&#146;t you give a pull on that rope?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " ohh we&#146;re not sailing.", "answer": " just pull on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " all right.  hey-hey-hey!!  sandwiches!", "answer": " what else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  here you go.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " ohh, sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " ohh whoops.", "answer": " careful! you&#146;re wasting good pastrami!  oh my god! i&#146;m my dad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}]